<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thoughts on</title><link>https://johnhorsema.github.io/categories/thoughts/</link><description>Recent content in Thoughts on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:19:42 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://johnhorsema.github.io/categories/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chatbot Isn't the Solution to Everything</title><link>https://johnhorsema.github.io/blog/chatbot-isnt-the-solution-to-everything/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:19:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://johnhorsema.github.io/blog/chatbot-isnt-the-solution-to-everything/</guid><description>In the era of advanced technology, it&amp;rsquo;s tempting to believe that chatbots hold the answer to all our customer engagement needs. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to approach this notion with a critical mindset. While chatbots have undoubtedly made significant progress, we must acknowledge that they are not a one-size-fits-all solution. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why this is the case.
Evolution of Chatbots # Chatbots have come a long way, thanks to the advancements in large language models.</description></item><item><title>In 2022, Blockchain is Here to Stay</title><link>https://johnhorsema.github.io/blog/in-2022-blockchain-is-here-to-stay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 09:19:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://johnhorsema.github.io/blog/in-2022-blockchain-is-here-to-stay/</guid><description>TL;DR # The crypto industry faced significant challenges in 2022, including breaches on cross-chain bridges, crashes, bankruptcies, and distrust among users. However, blockchain technology remains strong and transformative across various industries.
The vulnerabilities and attacks in the crypto space are often due to the implementation and security measures surrounding cryptocurrencies and decentralized finance platforms, not the blockchain technology itself.
To avoid risks, users should be cautious of projects with red flags, conduct thorough research on a project&amp;rsquo;s true utility, and evaluate its potential impact and long-term viability before making investment decisions.</description></item><item><title>Why I Enjoy Joining Hackathons</title><link>https://johnhorsema.github.io/blog/why-i-enjoy-joining-hackathons/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 09:19:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://johnhorsema.github.io/blog/why-i-enjoy-joining-hackathons/</guid><description>On April 22, I joined hackUST 2017, a hackathon organized by HKUST Entrepreneurship Center. For those who are still wondering: A hackathon is an event where groups of designers, idea-generators, technology experts get together to solve a problem under 24 or 36 hours, backed by technology and business ideas.
I wrote this piece because I wanted to not only document what happened, but raise awareness on hacker’s mentality.
How It Began # People join hackathons for all sorts of reasons:</description></item></channel></rss>